BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.830598: Mt. Diablo CA Unified School District (teachers) and Mount Diablo Education Association (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Code no.830631: Duval County FL School District (united office personnel of duval) and American Federation of Teachers / Duval Teachers Union, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Code no.830635: Baltimore City public schools (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Baltimore Teachers Union, Local 340, 1993-2005 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Code no.830645: Phoenix Union High School District (classified) and Classified Employees Assembly, 2001-2007 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Code no.830646: Broward County Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, 1999-2004 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Code no.830651: Dayton City School District (teachers) and Dayton Education Association, 2000-2003 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Code no.830677: Jefferson County KY Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association, 1988-1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Code no.830684: Detroit Board of Education (paraprofessionals) and American Federation of Teachers, 1986-2002 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Code no.830688: Brentwood NY Union Free School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Brentwood Teachers Association, 1996-2001 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Code no.830695: New York City Board of Education (paraprofessionals) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1992-2002 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Code no.830697: Connecticut, University of (faculty) and American Association of University Professors, 1993-2001 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Code no.830703: Memphis City Schools (teachers & related) and Memphis Education Association, 1988-2005 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Code no.830705: South Bend Community School Corp (teachers) and National Education Association, 1996-2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Code no.830706: Robbinsdale MN Area Independant School District 281 (teachers) and Robbinsdale Federation of Teachers, Local 872, 1985-1999 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Code no.830707: Frederick County MD Board of Education (teachers & certif) and National Education Association / Frederick County Teachers Association, 1995-2003 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Code no.830708: Toms River NJ Regional School (teachers & related) and Toms River Education Association, 2000- 2003 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Code no.830709: Prince Georges County MD Board of Education (classifed) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2250, 1997-2003 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Code no.830712: Palm Beach County School District (Regular workers) and Service Employees International Union / National Conference of Firemen and Oilers, Local 1227, 1983-2002 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Code no.830714: Anne Arundel County Board of Education (classif) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1693, 1998-2000 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Code no.830715: Palm Beach County School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Palm Beach County Classroom Teachers Association, 1993-2000 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Code no.830718: Sarasota County School Board (classified) and Sarasota County Teachers Association, 1993-2003 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Code no.830719: New York, City University of (blue collar) and Various, 2000-2000 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Code no.830720: Sarasota County School Board (teachers & cert) and Sarasota County Teachers Association, 1982- 2002 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Code no.830721: Milwaukee Board of School Directors (rec unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1616-888J, 1992-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Code no.830722: Evansville-Vanderburg IN School Corp (teachers) and National Education Association / Evansville Teachers Association, 1990-2001 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Code no.830723: Shawnee KS Board of Education District 512 (teachers) and National Education Association, 1996-2003 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Code no.830724: Clay County FL School Board (teachers) and Clay County Education Association, 1994-2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Code no.830725: Orange County CA (supervisors unit) and Orange County Employees Association, 1994-2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Code no.830726: Prince Georges County MD Board of Education (teachers) and Prince Georges County Education Association, 1997- 2006 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Code no.830727: Hillsborough County FL Board of Education (educational support) and National Education Association / Hillsborough County Teachers Association, 1993-2007 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Code no.830728: New York, City University of (white collar) and Various, 1994-2003 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Code no.830729: Chicago Board of Education (general unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 73, 1996-2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Code no.830730: San Diego Unified School District (office, technical, business) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 788, 1983-1992 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Code no.830731: Chicago Board of Education (cafeteria) and UNITE HERE, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Code no.830732: District of Columbia Board of Education (custodial) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 639, Local 730, 1982-1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Code no.830733: Pinellas County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association / Pinellas County Teachers Association, 1998-2004 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Code no.830734: Compton Unified School District (teachers) and Compton Education Association, 1995-2001 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Code no.830735: Pinellas County School Board (custodial) and Service Employees International Union / International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 1221, 1991-2000 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Code no.830737: New York City Board of Educucation (supervisors & administrators) and American Federation of School Administrators / Civil Service Association, Local 1, 1987-1996 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Code no.830740: Utica MI Community School District (teachers) and Utica Eduation Association, 1988-2002 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Code no.830741: Edmonds WA School District 15 (certificated) and Edmonds Education Association, 1994-2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Code no.830742: Broward County Board of Education (maintenance & transportation) and Marine Engineers Beneficial Association / Federation of Public Employees, 2001-2004 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Code no.830743: Little Rock School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Little Rock Classroom Teachers Association, 1982-2003 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Code no.830744: Salem OR Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association, 2000-2002 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Code no.830745: San Jose Unified School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 1985-1998 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Code no.830747: Los Angeles Community College (faculty) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 1521, 1996-2002 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Code no.830748: Los Angeles Unified School District (teachers) and National Education Association / United Teachers Los Angeles, 1995- 2000 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Code no.830749: Anne Arundel County Board of Education (clerical & e assistantt) and National Education Association / Secretaries and Assistants Association of Anne Arundel County, 1987-2000 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Code no.830750: Rochester NY Board of Education (classified) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Board of Education Non-Teaching Employees, Local 2419, 2000-2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Code no.830751: New York City Board of Education (administrative support) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1992-2002 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Code no.830752: California State University (operations support, Units 2,5,7,9) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000, 1996-2005 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Code no.830753: California State University (academic support., Unit 4) and American Federation of Teachers, 1988-2005 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Code no.830754: Los Angeles Community College (clerical & technical) and American Federation of Teachers / College Staff Guild 15521, 1990-2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Code no.830755: San Diego Unified School District (operations support service ) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 724, 1983-1999 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Code no.830756: San Diego Unified School District (paraeducators) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 759, 1992-2001 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Code no.830757: MInternational Association of Machinistsi-Dade County Public Schools (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1184, 1997-2003 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Code no.830758: California State University (faculty & librarian, Unit 3) and Service Employees International Union / California Faculty Association, Local 1983, 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Code no.830759: Sacramento City Unified School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Sacramento City Teachers Association, 1988-2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Code no.830760: Kenosha Unified School District 1 (teachers) and Kenosha Education Association, 1992-2003 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Code no.830762: Hartford CT Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 1018, 1985-2002 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Code no.830763: Seminole County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association, 1981-1999 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Code no.830764: Sacramento City Unified School District (classified) and Service Employees International Union, Local 790, 1995- 2002 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Code no.830765: Lee County FL School Board (support personnel) and Support Personnel Association of Lee County, 1997-2003 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Code no.830766: Lee County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association, 1996-2005 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Code no.830768: Orange County FL School Board (classified) and Orange Education Support Professionals Association, 1996- 2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Code no.830769: Orange County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association / Orange County Classroom Teachers Association, 1996-2002 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Code no.830770: Syracuse Board of Education (teachers & aux service) and National Education Association / Syracuse Teachers Association, Unit 1, 1988-2006 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Code no.830771: Springfield School Board (teachers) and Springfield Education Association, 1988-1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Code no.830772: Yonkers Public Schools (teachers) and Yonkers Federatin of Teachers, 1989-2001 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Code no.830773: Bridgeport (teachers) and Marine Engineers Beneficial Association / Federation of Public Employees, 1986-2003 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Code no.830774: Manatee County FL Board of Education (faculty) and Manatee Education Association, 1994-2002 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Code no.830775: Los Angeles Unified School District (teacher assistants-Unit F) and Service Employees International Union, Local 99, 1991- 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Code no.830776: Pinellas County School Board (support services) and National Education Association / Pinellas Education Support Personnel Association, 1990-2004 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Code no.830779: Bay County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association, 1990-2002 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Code no.830780: Bay County FL School Board (support) and National Education Association / Bay Education Support Personnel Association, 1991-2003 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Code no.830781: Duluth Independent School District 709 (clerical) and Duluth Federation of Teachers, Local 692, 1997-2001 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Code no.830782: Stamford Board of Education (teachers) and Stamford Education Association, 1992-2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Code no.830783: Garden Grove CA Unified School District (classified) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Ch. 121, 1995-2006 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Code no.830787: Fort Wayne Community Schools (teachers) and National Education Association, 1995-2007 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Code no.830788: Illinois, University of (clerical) and Service Employees International Union, Local 73, 1997-2006 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Code no.830789: Leon County FL Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Leon County Teachers Association, 2002-2004 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Code no.830790: San Diego Community College District (faculty) and American Federation of Teachers / San Diego Community College Guild 1931, 1990-2002 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Code no.830792: Jordan UT School District (classified) and Jordan Classified Employee Association, 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Code no.830793: Livonia MI School District (teachers & professionals) and Livonia Education Association, 1992-1999 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Code no.830796: San Diego Unified School District (teachers) and San Diego Education Association, 1995-2008 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Code no.830797: San Juan Unified School District (general unit) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 127, 1992-2001 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Code no.830798: Garden Grove CA Unified School District (teachers) and Garden Grove Education Association, 2001-2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Code no.830800: Albuquerque Municipal School District 12 (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 1420, 1992- 2002 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Code no.830803: San Juan Unified School District (teachers) and National Education Association / San Juan Teachers Association, 1995- 2004 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Code no.830804: Illinois, University of (Champaign-Urbana-clerical & administrative) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 3700, 1992-2001 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Code no.830805: Jefferson Parish LA Board of Education (teachers & related) and Jefferson Federation of Teachers, Local 1559, 1993-2004 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Code no.830806: Miami-Dade County Public Schools (maintenance) and Dade County School Maintenance Employee Committee, 1993- 2002 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Code no.830807: Miami-Dade County Public Schools (teachers & clerical) and American Federation of Teachers / United Teachers of Dade, 1997-2002 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Code no.830808: Sioux Falls SD Public Schools (teachers) and National Education Association, 2000-2003 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Code no.830810: Oakland Unified Schools (teachers & profess) and Oakland Education Association, 1995-2002 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Code no.830813: Davenport Community School District (teachers) and Davenport Education Association, 1997-2002 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Code no.830814: Wayne State University (technical, office & professional) (WSU Staff Assoc) and United Auto Workers, Local 2071, 1992-2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Code no.830816: San Francisco Unified School District (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / United Educators of San Francisco, 1992-2001 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Code no.830817: San Francisco Unified School District (support) and American Federation of Teachers / United Educators of San Francisco, 1992-2001 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Code no.830818: Parkway MO Public Schools (teachers & related professionals) and National Education Association, 1993- 1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Code no.830819: Worcester School Committee (teachers) and Education Association of Worcester, 1992-2007 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Code no.830820: Duval County FL School District (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Duval Teachers Union, 1999- 2002 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Code no.830821: Alachua County FL School Board (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, 1992-2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Code no.830822: Alachua County FL School Board (career service employees) and American Federation of Teachers, 1997-2002 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Code no.830823: Volusia County Board of Education (office) and Volusia Educational Support Association, 1992-2005 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Code no.830826: Carroll County Board of Education (teachers) and Carroll County Education Association, 2001-2005 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Code no.830828: Christiana School District (teachers-Wilmington) and National Education Association, 2001-2007 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Code no.830830: Long Beach (nonsupervisory) and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1930, 1993-2004 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Code no.830831: Fremont CA Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association, 1998-2004 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Code no.830832: West Contra Costa Unified School District (classified) and Public Employees Union, Local 1, 1999-2002 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Code no.830833: Kansas City KS Board of Education (teachers) Dist 500 and National Education Association of Kansas City, 1994- 2005 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Code no.830834: Topeka Unified School District 501 (teachers & related) and National Education Association of Topeka, 1996- 2003 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Code no.830835: Long Beach Unified School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Teachers Association of Long Beach, 2000-2007 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Code no.830836: California, University of (non-senate instruct.) and University of California - American Federation of Teachers, 2003- 2006 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Code no.830837: California State (psychiatric technicians, Unit 18) and California Association of Psychiatric Technicians, 1982- 2003 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Code no.830838: California State (allied services, Unit 15) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000, 1995-2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Code no.830839: California State (office & allied, Unit 4) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000, 1999-2003 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Code no.830840: California State (crAmerican Federation of Teacherss & maintenance, Unit 12) and International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 3, Local 12, Local 39, Local 501, 1992-2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Code no.830841: California, University of (clerical & allied services, Unit 12) and Coalition of University Employees, 1994- 2006 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Code no.830842: California, University of (service, Unit 11) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1995- 2004 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Code no.830843: California, University of (patient care tech, Unit 13) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 2002-2007 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Code no.830844: California, University of (RNs, Unit 7) and California Nurses Association, 1993-2002 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Code no.830847: Broward County Board of Education (food service) and Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1994-2003 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Code no.830850: Seattle Community College District 6 (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Seattle Community College Teachers, Local 1789, 1988-2002 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Code no.830851: Kansas City (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 500, 1994- 1998 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Code no.840003: Los Angeles County Metro Transportation Authority (drivers & operators) and United Transportation Union (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Code no.840009: Los Angeles County Metro Transportation Authority (mechanical & mainenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1277, 1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Code no.840010: Allegheny County Port Authority (operators & mechanics) and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1996- 2007 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Code no.840011: Chicago Parks Dept. (general unit) and Service Employees International Union, Local 73, 1995-2001 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Code no.840012: Fremont CA Board of Education (teachers) and Community College Association, 1990-2005 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Code no.840014: Dade County Transit Agency (operating) and Transport Workers Union of America, Local 291, 1990-2005 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Code no.840015: East St. Louis School District 189 (teachers & others) and East St. Louis Federation of Teachers, Local 1220, 1992-2002 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Code no.840016: Yonkers Public Schools (nonteaching unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 860, 1992-2001 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Code no.840018: Maryland Mass Transit Authority (operating & maintenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1300, 1999- 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Code no.840019: Chicago Transit Authority (operationss & maintenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 241, Local 308, 1993-1999 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Code no.840020: Oregon, University of (grad students-Eugene) and American Federation of Teachers / Graduate Teaching Fellows Federation, 1995-2002 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Code no.840021: Ventura County Community College District (faculty) and American Federation of Teachers / Ventura County Federation of College Teachers, 1994-2001 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Code no.840023: Orleans LA Parish School Board (paraeducators) and American Federation of Teachers / United Teachers of New Orleans, Local 527, 1997-2003 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Code no.840024: Lowell MA (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / United Teachers of Lowell, Local 495, 1994-2004 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Code no.840025: Greater Cleveland Regional Transit (operators) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 268, 1988-2000 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Code no.840026: Vallejo City United School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 1995-2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Code no.840030: New York City Transit Authority (administrative, engineers & architects) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 375, 1988-1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Code no.840031: King County WA Metro Transit (operations, maintenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587, 1995- 2004 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Code no.840032: Jefferson County CO School District (classified) and Civil Service Employees Association, 1994-1999 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Code no.840033: Indiana State (units 4-7) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 62, 1992- 2001 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Code no.840034: Indiana State (units 1-3 and 10) and United Auto Workers / American Federation of Teachers, Local 9212, 1995- 2007 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Code no.840035: Camden County (blue & white collar) and New Jersey Civil Service Association, Co. 10, 1997-2007 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Code no.840036: San Antonio VIA Transit System (bus operators) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 694, 1997-1999 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Code no.840037: Ramsey MN County (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 8, Co. 14, 2000-2008 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Code no.840038: St. Louis Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 420, 2001-2004 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Code no.840039: Columbus, City of (supervisors--mid managers) and Columbus Municipal Association of Government Employees, 1995- 2005 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Code no.840040: New Jersey Turnpike Authority (operations, maintenance & tolls) and International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 194, 1995-2003 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Code no.840041: Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority (general unit) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 589, 1994- 1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Code no.840042: Boise City Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association, 1995-2001 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Code no.840043: Warwick public schools (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, Warwick Teachers Union, Local 915, 1994- 2000 (Box 36, Folder 22)